In this video we have an example of nesting.
在这段视频中，我们有一个嵌套的例子。
In function f we have a while loop with an if statement inside of it.
在函数 f 中，我们有一个 while 循环，里面有一个 if 语句。在
And inside of the if statement there is a for loop.
if 语句里面有一个 for 循环。
The important thing to remember with nesting is that there's
在嵌套时要记住的重要一点是，
really nothing special about it.
它真的没有什么特别之处。
We follow the same rules we've always see.
我们遵循我们一直看到的相同规则。
We being with our execution arrow at the start of main.
我们在 main 的开头处使用执行箭头。
And the first thing we're going to do is call f, passing 3 for a, and 8 for b.
我们要做的第一件事就是调用 f，传递 3 表示 a，传递 8 表示 b。
We create a frame, as always.
我们一如既往地创建一个框架。
And we're going to remember where we're going to return, and
我们要记住要返回的位置，然后
begin executing code inside of f.
开始在 f 中执行代码。由
Since a less than b is true, we're going to go inside the body of the while loop.
于 a 小于 b 是真的，所以我们要进入 while 循环的主体。
We print a equals 3, b equals 8.
我们打印 a 等于 3，b 等于 8。
And then we reach an if statement that checks if a mod 2 is 0.
然后我们得到一个 if 语句，用于检查 mod 2 是否为 0。
Remember that percent is the mod operator,
请记住，百分比是模组运算符
which computes the remainder when you do division.
，当你进行除法时，它会计算余数。
3 divided by 2 has a remainder of 1, so 3 mod 2 is 1.
3 除以 2 的余数为 1，因此 3 模组 2 等于 1。
a mod 2 is not zero, so this conditional expression is false, and
a mod 2 不为零，所以这个条件表达式为假，
we skip over the if statement.
我们跳过 if 语句。
>> a++ increments a to 4, and b-- decrements b to 7.
>> a++ 将 a 递增到 4，而 b--将 b 递减到 7。
Now we've reached the end of the while loop.
现在我们已经到了 while 循环的尽头。
So we jump to back to the beginning, and test it's condition again.
因此，我们回到起点，然后再次测试它的状况。
a less than b is true, so we enter the body and print a=4, b=7.
a 小于 b 是真的，所以我们输入正文并打印 a=4，b=7。
Now when we look at a mod 2, 4 mod 2 is 0.
现在，当我们看模组 2 时，4 模组 2 是 0。
0 = 0 is true, so we enter the if statement.
0 = 0 为真，因此我们输入 if 语句。
Now we have a for loop.
现在我们有一个 for 循环。
It's going to declare an int i, and initialize it to the value of a.
它会声明一个 int i，然后将其初始化为 a 的值。
So we make a box for i, and set it equal to 4.
所以我们为 i 做一个方框，然后将其设置为 4。
We then test the condition of the for loop.
然后我们测试 for 循环的状态。
4 less than 7 is true, so we enter the body of the for loop.
4 小于 7 是真的，所以我们输入 for 循环的主体。
We print i = 4.
我们打印 i = 4。
Then we perform the increment statement assigning 5 to i,
然后我们执行增量语句，将 5 赋给 i，
and return to the begging of the loop.
然后返回循环的开端。
We check the condition again.
我们再次检查状况。
5 less than 7 is true, so we enter the for loop again, we print i = 5.
5 小于 7 是真的，所以我们再次进入 for 循环，我们打印 i = 5。
Then we increment i to 6, and return to the beginning of the loop.
然后我们将 i 递增到 6，然后返回到循环的开头。
We repeat this process.
我们重复这个过程。
6 less than 7, print i = 6.
6 小于 7，打印 i = 6。将
Increment i to 7, and return to the beginning.
i 增量为 7，然后返回到起点。
This time, 7 less than 7 is false.
这次，7 小于 7 是错误的。
So we skip past the four loop, leaving the scope of i.
因此，我们跳过了四个循环，留下了 i 的作用域。
And continue executing.
然后继续执行。
We're now at the end of the if statement's body,
我们现在处于 if 语句正文的末尾，
so we resume executing right after it.
因此我们将在它之后立即恢复执行。
We increment a to 5 and decrement b to 6, and now we're at the end of the y loop.
我们将 a 递增到 5，将 b 减为 6，现在我们已经走到了 y 循环的尽头。
So we jumped back to the top.
于是我们跳回了山顶。
A less than b is still true.
小于 b 的 A 仍然是正确的。
So we enter the body, we print a=5, b=6.
所以我们进入正文，我们打印 a=5，b=6。
We check a mod 2.
我们检查一个模组 2.
5 mod 2 is 1, 1=0 is false, so we skip the if statement.
5 mod 2 是 1，1=0 是假的，所以我们跳过 if 语句。
We increment a to 6 and decrement b to 5.
我们将 a 递增到 6，将 b 减为 5。
And return to the top of the while loop.
然后返回到 while 循环的顶部。
6 less than 5 is false.
6 小于 5 是错误的。
So we skip over the body of the while loop, reaching the end of the function.
因此，我们跳过 while 循环的主体，到达函数的末尾。
This causes us to return to main.
这会导致我们返回主页面。
The only thing left in main is the return statement, so
main 中唯一剩下的就是 return 语句，所以
we return 0 and exit the program.
我们返回 0 然后退出程序。